BRYAN SILVA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

◆ ARGENTINA

◆ +54 342 522-0522

• DETAILS •

Argentina +54 342 522-0522 brandonb2816@gmail.com

> Nationality Venezuelan

• LINKS •

Linkedln

Github

Portfolio

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Tailwind

VueJS

React

PHP, Laravel

SEO & Web Performance

GA, GTM, Data Studio

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

HOBBIES

Cryptocurrencies, NFT's, Artificial Intelligence

PROFILE

I am a self-taught Front-End developer started 4 years ago. I have knowledge in layout with HTML5, CSS (Grid, Flexbox, Sass Bootstrap, Tailwind). Webpack management for task automation. I have JavaScript ES6 knowledge as well as JQuery knowledge. I have made personal projects with these technologies that I keep in my Github repositories. I also have experience in developing Wordpress websites.

I have knowledge in VueJS and ReactJS, I am currently learning Next JS and Gatsby.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Front-End Developer at Leadbox HQ, Canadá

2020 - Present

I am currently working in the Core Team developing new features, I am also in charge of improving the Core Web Vitals of each of the sites so that they have a good performance. I use SEO tools such as Ahrefs to check the status of the sites and make the corresponding corrections. I also take care of the development of new sites and the creation of Google Analytics accounts and customized Data Studio reports.

Front-End Developer at Fundación EPyCA, Argentina

2020 - 2020

I was in charge of converting some old Flash views into HTML and CSS and fixing some bugs in the Reprasis system, a platform of the foundation, so that it could work properly before the start of the course at the University of Buenos Aires (UBA).

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science applied to Multimedia and Website Design, Universidad Nacional del Litoral, Argentina

2020 - 2023

Platzi

2018 - 2022